Guide to the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 46 records, 1910-2009; 5739-001; 26.52 cubic feet 31 boxes
  - Series III: Contract Negotiations, 1950-2009 (Box-folder 16/1-16/47; 17/1-17/61; 18/1-18/40; 19/1-19/43; 21/1-21/94; 22/1-22/68; 23/1-23/78; 24/1-24/74; 25/1-25/86; 26/1-26/97; 27/1-27/73; 28/1-28/101; 29/1-29/94; 30/1-30/64)
    - Subseries B: Contract Negotiations Part 2, 1952-2009 (Box-folder 21/1-21/94; 22/1-22/68; 23/1-23/78; 24/1-24/74; 25/1-25/86; 26/1-26/97; 27/1-27/73; 28/1-28/101; 29/1-29/94; 30/1-30/64)
      - Bowie Electric, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 22/4)
      - Bowie Electric, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 22/5)
      - Bowlake Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1975-1984 (Box-folder 22/6)
      - Bremer Corporation (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 22/7)
      - Bremerton Naval Shipyards - Dept. of the Navy Contract Negotiations, 1985 (Box-folder 22/8)
      - Briarkirk Enterprises, Inc. D/B/A Briarkirk E/E (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2005 (Box-folder 22/9)
      - Briarkirk Enterprises, Inc. D/B/A Briarkirk E/E (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 22/10)
      - Broadview Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1965-1983 (Box-folder 22/11)
      - Broadway Electric Company Contract Negotiations, 1961-1992 (Box-folder 22/12)
      - Brothers Electric Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 22/13)
      - Build, Design & Develop LLC (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 22/14)
      - Building Control Systems Contract Negotiations, 1987 (Box-folder 22/15)
      - Building Owners and Managers Association Contract Negotiations, 1954-1977 (Box-folder 22/16)
      - Bumstead-Woolford Co. Contract Negotiations, 1966-1986 (Box-folder 22/17)
      - Burglar Stop USA (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2004 (Box-folder 22/18)
      - Burien-Wagner Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 22/19)
      - Burke Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box-folder 22/20)
      - Business Music Co. F/K/A Music-Vend Distributing Co. Contract Negotiations, 1961-1981 (Box-folder 22/21)
      - Business Telephone Systems Contract Negotiations, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 22/22)
      - Bussell Electric Co. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22/23)
      - Cable Splicing Plus Contract Negotiations, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 22/24)
      - C.A.E. & Associates, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 22/25)
      - C.A.E. & Associates, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 22/26)
      - C.A.E. & Associates, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 22/27)
      - Campbell Electric Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1965-1977, 1991 (Box-folder 22/28)
      - Canaday Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 22/29)
      - Canaday Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box-folder 22/30)
      - C & M Electric, Inc Contract Negotiations, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 22/31)
      - Canem Electrical-Mechanical Systems Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1979-1992 (Box-folder 22/32)
      - Carib Electric LLC (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 22/33)
      - Carlsen and Winquist Oil Co. Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box-folder 22/34)
      - John A. Carlson Electric Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1955-1988 (Box-folder 22/35)
      - John A. Carlson Electric Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 22/36)
      - John A. Carlson Electric Co., Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 22/37)
      - Cascade Electric Contract Negotiations, 1971-1985 (Box-folder 22/38)
      - Cascade Machinery and Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1960-1989 (Box-folder 22/39)
      - Cascade Oil Co. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 22/40)
      - Cascade Oil Co. Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box-folder 22/41)
      - C.B. Manchester Contract Negotiations, 1993 (Box-folder 22/42)
      - Carstens and Humphreys Contract Negotiations, 1956-1988 (Box-folder 22/43)
      - Catalytic, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1986 (Box-folder 22/44)
      - CCE, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 22/45)
      - CCE, Inc. (Sound and Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 22/46)
      - CCE, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 22/47)
      - C.D.I. Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1987-1996 (Box-folder 22/48)
      - Cedar Creek Electric LLC (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2009 (Box-folder 22/49)
      - Center Electric Co./Fred Peterson Construction Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 22/50)
      - Central Burner Service Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 22/51)
      - Central Electric Communications (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2006 (Box-folder 22/52)
      - Central Electric Communications (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 22/53)
      - Central Telecom (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22/54)
      - Central T.V., Inc. Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1967-1981 (Box-folder 22/55)
      - Central T.V., Inc. Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1967-1981 (Box-folder 22/56)
      - C.E. Skinner, Inc. - Burien Library Contract Negotiations, 1993 (Box-folder 22/57)
      - Champion Electric Service LLC (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 22/58)
      - Bill Chapman Electric Contract Negotiations, 1960-1976 (Box-folder 22/59)
      - Chapman Electric D/B/A Holman's Chapman Electric, Inc. Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1966-1999 (Box-folder 22/60)
      - Character Electric Contract Negotiations, 1972 (Box-folder 22/61)
      - Charter Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 22/62)
      - Chelan Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations (Box-folder 22/63)
      - Chelan Electric (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 22/64)
      - Cherry Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 22/65)
      - Children's Hospital and Medical Center - Seattle Building and Construction Trades Council Contract Negotiations, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 22/66)
      - Chinook Electrical Services, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997, 2009 (Box-folder 22/67)
      - Chin's Electric, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 22/68)
      - Christenson Services, LLC F/K/A Christenson Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 23/1)
      - Christenson Services, LLC F/K/A Christenson Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 23/2)
      - Christenson Services, LLC F/K/A Christenson Electric (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1994-2001 (Box-folder 23/3)
      - Christenson Services, LLC F/K/A Christenson Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1976-2002 (Box-folder 23/4)
      - Christenson Technology Services, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 23/5)
      - Christenson Technology Services, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 23/6)
      - Christenson Technology Services, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 23/7)
      - Circle Electric, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 23/8)
      - City Electric & Fixture Company Contract Negotiations, 1971-1982 (Box-folder 23/9)
      - City Transfer Company Contract Negotiations, 1966-1974, 1985 (Box-folder 23/10)
      - City Transfer Heat and Oil Contract Negotiations, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 23/11)
      - C.J. Hughes Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 23/12)
      - Cleander Electric Contract Negotiations, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 23/13)
      - Clear Communications, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 23/14)
      - Clinton Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1968-1989 (Box-folder 23/15)
      - C.M.J., Inc. (Sound Intercommunication and Telephone Interconnect) Contract Negotiations, 1980 (Box-folder 23/16)
      - Coast Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1977-1994 (Box-folder 23/17)
      - Cochran Electric Co., Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 23/18)
      - Cochran Electric Co., Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 23/19)
      - Collier Construction, Inc. (Inside Wire, Residential, Lighting Maintenance & Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1983 (Box-folder 23/20)
      - Collins Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 23/21)
      - Collins Electric Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 23/22)
      - Collins Electric Co. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box-folder 23/23)
      - Collins Electrical Construction Co. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 23/24)
      - Collins & Hedges Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 23/25)
      - Columbia River Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 23/26)
      - Coumbine Cable Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 23/27)
      - Coumbine Cable Co., Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2000 (Box-folder 23/28)
      - Combustion & Control, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1972-1994 (Box-folder 23/29)
      - Commerce Electric Corp. Contract Negotiations, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 23/30)
      - Commercial Electric Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1971-1996 (Box-folder 23/31)
      - Commercial Electric Co., Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 23/32)
      - Commercial Electrical Contractors, Inc. (Inside Wire & Light Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1979-1992 (Box-folder 23/33)
      - Commercial Service Electric Contract Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23/34)
      - Commonwealth Electric Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1985-1995 (Box-folder 23/35)
      - Commplus Associates LLC (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 23/36)
      - Communication Services (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 23/37)
      - Communication Specialists, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 23/38)
      - L.K. Comstock & Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 23/39)
      - Concrete Coring Co. Contract Negotiations, 1967-1973, 1996 (Box-folder 23/40)
      - Concrete Cutting Co. Contract Negotiations, 1973-1990 (Box-folder 23/41)
      - Concrete Pacific Sawing and Drilling Contract Negotiations, 1973-1990 (Box-folder 23/42)
      - Connected Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2007 (Box-folder 23/43)
      - Connect Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999, 2009 (Box-folder 23/44)
      - Conrex, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 23/45)
      - Consolidated Electric Corp. Contract Negotiations, 1969-1982 (Box-folder 23/46)
      - Continental Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 23/47)
      - Continental Electric (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 23/48)
      - Control Electric Systems Contract Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23/49)
      - Contrologic, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 23/50)
      - Contrologic, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 23/51)
      - Controls Installation Company of the Northwest D/B/A A.S.C.O., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 23/52)
      - Cooper Electric, Inc (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1992-2004 (Box-folder 23/53)
      - Cooper Electric, Inc (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 23/54)
      - Cornwall Fuel Company Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976, 1990 (Box-folder 23/55)
      - Corvallis Electricians, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 23/56)
      - Cottage Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1959-1975 (Box-folder 23/57)
      - CPB Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991 (Box-folder 23/58)
      - CPB Electric (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1991 (Box-folder 23/59)
      - Cristcat Washington Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 23/60)
      - Cross Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2009 (Box-folder 23/61)
      - F.T. Crowe & Co., Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1966-1980 (Box-folder 23/62)
      - Cupertino Electric Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 23/63)
      - Cupertino Electric Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 23/64)
      - Cupertino Electric Inc. D/B/A Ceitronics (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 23/65)
      - Current Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1979 (Box-folder 23/66)
      - Curtiss Enterprises F/K/A Blue Streak Electrical Contractor Contract Negotiations, 1975 (Box-folder 23/67)
      - Custom Cabling Northwest (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 23/68)
      - Custom Concrete Cutting, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 23/69)
      - Dahl Electric Contract Negotiations, 1981 (Box-folder 23/70)
      - D & B Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 23/71)
      - Darr and Darr Corp. Contract Negotiations, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 23/72)
      - Datatech Industries, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 23/73)
      - Dave Magera Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 23/74)
      - David A. Mowat Company Contract Negotiations, 1994 (Box-folder 23/75)
      - David Gleaves Company, Inc. (Marine) Contract Negotiations, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 23/76)
      - Davison's Appliance Contract Negotiations, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 23/77)
      - Del Guzzi Construction Contract Negotiations, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 23/78)
      - Delta Electric Contract Negotiations, 1972-2976 (Box-folder 24/1)
      - Delta Electric Contract Negotiations, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 24/2)
      - Deno Electric Contract Negotiations, 1983, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 24/3)
      - Department Stores - Seattle Building & Construction Trades Council Contract Negotiations, 1955-1981 (Box-folder 24/4)
      - Department Stores - Seattle Department Stores Association (Radio/TV/Appliances) Contract Negotiations, 1961-1979 (Box-folder 24/5)
      - Diamond Electric Contract Negotiations, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 24/6)
      - Diamond Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2005 (Box-folder 24/7)
      - Diesel Oil Sales Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box-folder 24/8)
      - Digital Controls Electric Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box-folder 24/9)
      - Diversified Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2002 (Box-folder 24/10)
      - Diversified Industries, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 24/11)
      - Diversified Industries, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1991 (Box-folder 24/12)
      - D.L.S. Co. Contract Negotiations, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 24/13)
      - Doc's Electric Contract Negotiations, 1983 (Box-folder 24/14)
      - Dome Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 24/15)
      - Doubleday Electric Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1983-2006 (Box-folder 24/16)
      - Drake Marine Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 24/17)
      - Drury Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 24/18)
      - Dryer Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 24/19)
      - Dryer and Sons Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 24/20)
      - Dugan Sound Company Contract Negotiations, 1982 (Box-folder 24/21)
      - Duracom Cabling, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 24/22)
      - D.W. Nicholson Contract Negotiations, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 24/23)
      - Dwyer Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, Part ½, 1989-1997 (Box-folder 24/24)
      - Dwyer Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, Part 2/2, 1989-1997 (Box-folder 24/25)
      - Dwyer Electric, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 24/26)
      - Eagle Crest Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 24/27)
      - Eagle Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1985-2006 (Box-folder 24/28)
      - Eagle Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2002 (Box-folder 24/29)
      - Eastside Electrical Services, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 24/30)
      - Eastside Electrical Services, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1985-1995 (Box-folder 24/31)
      - E.C. Ernst Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box-folder 24/32)
      - Eclipse Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 24/33)
      - Eclipse Electric (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 24/34)
      - Edison Electric (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 24/35)
      - E & E Contractors (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1967-1997 (Box-folder 24/36)
      - E & E Contractors (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1990 (Box-folder 24/37)
      - E.G. Middleton Company (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 24/38)
      - EL-CO Contractors, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 24/39)
      - Electrical Associates Construction, Inc. (Construction & Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1974-1989 (Box-folder 24/40)
      - Electrical Energy Contractors, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1988-2006 (Box-folder 24/41)
      - Electrical Motor and Equipment Shop Contractors Contract Negotiations, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 24/42)
      - Electrical Systems, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 24/43)
      - Electrical Technology Contract Negotiations, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 24/44)
      - Electrical West Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 24/45)
      - Electric Contractors, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1967-1976 (Box-folder 24/46)
      - Electric Controls, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1977 (Box-folder 24/47)
      - Electric Motors, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 24/48)
      - Electric Service, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 24/49)
      - Electric Shop of Lynnwood Contract Negotiations, 1989 (Box-folder 24/50)
      - Electric Smith (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 24/51)
      - Electriko, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1963-1984 (Box-folder 24/52)
      - Electrocon, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999-2006 (Box-folder 24/53)
      - Electromatic Sales and Service Contract Negotiations, 1957-1974 (Box-folder 24/54)
      - Electronic Services Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1973 (Box-folder 24/55)
      - Electro-Vox Intercom Co. of Seattle Contract Negotiations, 1968-1978 (Box-folder 24/56)
      - Emcon Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1977 (Box-folder 24/57)
      - Emerald City Electric Contract Negotiations, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 24/58)
      - Empire/Seven Sisters (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 24/59)
      - Encompass Electrical Technologies (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 24/60)
      - Encompass Electrical Technologies (Light Fixture) Contract Negotiations, 2002 (Box-folder 24/61)
      - Encompass Electrical Technologies (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2002 (Box-folder 24/62)
      - Encompass Electrical Technologies (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2002 (Box-folder 24/63)
      - Energy Electric Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 24/64)
      - Enigma Electric (Residential) Company Contract Negotiations, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 24/65)
      - Enos Communications (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 2006 (Box-folder 24/66)
      - Entrance Controls (Sound Intercommunications & Telephone Interconnect) Contract Negotiations, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 24/67)
      - Environmental Music Service, Inc. (Sound Intercommunications & Telephone Interconnect) Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box-folder 24/68)
      - Evans Products Company, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1962, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 24/69)
      - Evergreen Concrete Sawing Contract Negotiations, 1980 (Box-folder 24/70)
      - Evergreen Electrical Contractors (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1979-2001 (Box-folder 24/71)
      - Evergreen Electrical Contractors (Light Fixture Maintenance) Contract Negotiations, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 24/72)
      - Evergreen Electrical Contractors (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 24/73)
      - Evergreen Electrical Contractors (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 24/74)
      - Evergreen Technologies, Inc. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 25/1)
      - Executone Telecommunications Northwest, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1960-1983 (Box-folder 25/2)
      - Expert Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 25/3)
      - Eyelander Electric Motor Supply, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1977 (Box-folder 25/4)
      - E-Z Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 25/5)
      - E-Z Electric, Inc. (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 25/6)
      - Farnham Electric Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box-folder 25/7)
      - Federal Sign Company Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 25/8)
      - Feltus Electric Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box-folder 25/9)
      - Fiber Optic Distributors, Inc.(Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 25/10)
      - Fields Electric (Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 25/11)
      - Fiesta Electric, Inc. D/B/A Circle Electric Contract Negotiations, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 25/12)
      - Finish Electric Company, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 25/13)
      - Firecom Systems, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 25/14)
      - Firecom Systems, Inc. (Sound Intercommunication & Telephone Interconnect) Contract Negotiations, 1979 (Box-folder 25/15)
      - First Class Electric, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 25/16)
      - First Class Electric, Inc. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 1999 (Box-folder 25/17)
      - First Class Electric, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2003 (Box-folder 25/18)
      - Fischbach and Moore, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1961-1983 (Box-folder 25/19)
      - Fischbach and Moore, Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1978, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 25/20)
      - Fischbach and Moore, Inc. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 25/21)
      - Five Star Electric Contract Negotiations, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 25/22)
      - Fletcher Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1956-1982 (Box-folder 25/23)
      - Fletcher General, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 25/24)
      - FM Electric, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 25/25)
      - Fox Electric Co. F/K/A Fox & Nystrum Electric Co. Contract Negotiations, 1956-1986 (Box-folder 25/26)
      - Fox Electric Co. (Residential) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 25/27)
      - Fox Electric Co. (Sound & Communication) Contract Negotiations, 1993-2003 (Box-folder 25/28)
      - Fox Electric Co. (Stockman) Contract Negotiations, 2001 (Box-folder 25/29)
      - Frahler Electric Co., Inc. (Inside Wire) Contract Negotiations, 1998-2008 (Box-folder 25/30)